http://www.travelblog.org/privacy.html

Africa Antarctica Asia C. America & Caribbean Europe Middle East N. America Oceania Oceans & Seas S. America
Create a Travel Blog Bloggers Blogs Wallpaper Travel Guide Travel Photos Cheap Travel Insurance Forum Photos
Africa Antarctica Asia C. America & Caribbean Europe Middle East N. America Oceania Oceans & Seas S. America
Privacy Policy for TravelBlog.orgGeneral InformationIf you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us.At travelblog.org, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information that is received and collected by travelblog.org and how it is used.Please be aware that privacy laws in each territory may differ. travelblog.org adheres to the privacy laws in the United States of America.travelblog.org reserves the right to change or update this privacy policy at any time.Log FilesLike many other Web sites, travelblog.org makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.Cookies and Web Beaconstravelblog.org does not directly use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.travelblog.org does use cookies to maintain user sessions, allow login and use the site in an interactive capacity. These cookies will last the length of your browser session.travelblog.org uses Google Analytics to analyze the use of this website. Google Analytics generates statistical and other information about website use by means of cookies, which are stored on users' computers. The information generated relating to our website is used to create reports about the use of the website. Google will store this information. Google's privacy policy is available at Google's websiteDoubleClick DART CookieGoogle, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on travelblog.org.Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to travelblog.org and other sites on the Internet.Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL - http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.htmlSome of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include ....Google AdsenseAmazonCatcha Digital AsiaGlobaltrotting Digital MediaThese third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on travelblog.org send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.travelblog.org has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. travelblog.org's privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites. travelblog.org has no control over the privacy policies of these third-parties.If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers' respective websites.TravelBlog.org Email Policytravelblog.org will not sell or distribute your email address to third parties unless you give explicit permission.travelblog.org will not spam your account, we will allow third parties to email you through a custom messaging system and will do our utmost to ensure that spam does not get sent on to you. Unless you respond directly to these emails, the third party will not be able to obtain your email address.If you leave your email address through either the messaging system or comments on a bloggers page, that blogger will have access to your email address, travelblog.org is not able to control what happens with your email address beyond this point. To ensure privacy, you may join travelblog.org and only your travelblog account will be visible when you comment.Please see our Terms of Service for details on how we operate and your expected conduct when visiting or using this site.
Tot: 0.005s; Tpl: 0.002s; cc: 0; qc: 0; dbt: s; 0;
w:www (104.131.125.221); sld: 1;
; mem: 1mb
